{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Floor Cleaners For Your Business","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/61320/":{"taskOID":61320,"originalTaskOID":61320,"setID":7243,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":501552,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of cleaning would you like?","shortQuestionText":"What kind of cleaning would you like?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202146,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Polishing / Buffing","answerDisplayText":"Polishing / Buffing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202148,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stripping","answerDisplayText":"Stripping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202149,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Waxing","answerDisplayText":"Waxing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202147,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501553,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of service is needed?","shortQuestionText":"What type of service is needed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":201817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time","answerDisplayText":"One time","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201809,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Recurring","answerDisplayText":"Recurring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501554,"questionDisplayText":"Area size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate size of the floor?","shortQuestionText":"What is the approximate size of the floor?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202132,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202133,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000-5,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1,000-5,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202134,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5,000-10,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"5,000-10,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202135,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 10,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7739,"questionDisplayText":"For how many locations/units is this request?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"For how many locations/units is this request?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20781,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20782,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20783,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-10","answerDisplayText":"6-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20784,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11+","answerDisplayText":"11+","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7738,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Business","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What type of business is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20773,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retail/Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Retail/Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20774,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Manufacturing/Industrial","answerDisplayText":"Manufacturing/Industrial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20775,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Property Management","answerDisplayText":"Property Management","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20776,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Government/Municipality","answerDisplayText":"Government/Municipality","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20777,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Service","answerDisplayText":"Service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20778,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"School/Church","answerDisplayText":"School/Church","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20779,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Health-care Facility","answerDisplayText":"Health-care Facility","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20780,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":501552,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of cleaning would you like?","shortQuestionText":"What kind of cleaning would you like?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202146,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Polishing / Buffing","answerDisplayText":"Polishing / Buffing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202148,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stripping","answerDisplayText":"Stripping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202149,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Waxing","answerDisplayText":"Waxing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202147,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":202146,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Polishing / Buffing","answerDisplayText":"Polishing / Buffing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202148,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stripping","answerDisplayText":"Stripping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202149,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Waxing","answerDisplayText":"Waxing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202147,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501553,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of service is needed?","shortQuestionText":"What type of service is needed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":201817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time","answerDisplayText":"One time","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201809,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Recurring","answerDisplayText":"Recurring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":201817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time","answerDisplayText":"One time","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201809,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Recurring","answerDisplayText":"Recurring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501554,"questionDisplayText":"Area size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate size of the floor?","shortQuestionText":"What is the approximate size of the floor?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202132,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202133,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000-5,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1,000-5,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202134,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5,000-10,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"5,000-10,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202135,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 10,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":202132,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202133,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000-5,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1,000-5,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202134,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5,000-10,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"5,000-10,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202135,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 10,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7739,"questionDisplayText":"For how many locations/units is this request?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"For how many locations/units is this request?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20781,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20782,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20783,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-10","answerDisplayText":"6-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20784,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11+","answerDisplayText":"11+","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20781,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20782,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20783,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-10","answerDisplayText":"6-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20784,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11+","answerDisplayText":"11+","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7738,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Business","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What type of business is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20773,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retail/Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Retail/Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20774,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Manufacturing/Industrial","answerDisplayText":"Manufacturing/Industrial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20775,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Property Management","answerDisplayText":"Property Management","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20776,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Government/Municipality","answerDisplayText":"Government/Municipality","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20777,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Service","answerDisplayText":"Service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20778,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"School/Church","answerDisplayText":"School/Church","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20779,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Health-care Facility","answerDisplayText":"Health-care Facility","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20780,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20773,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retail/Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Retail/Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20774,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Manufacturing/Industrial","answerDisplayText":"Manufacturing/Industrial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20775,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Property Management","answerDisplayText":"Property Management","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20776,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Government/Municipality","answerDisplayText":"Government/Municipality","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20777,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Service","answerDisplayText":"Service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20778,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"School/Church","answerDisplayText":"School/Church","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20779,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Health-care Facility","answerDisplayText":"Health-care Facility","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20780,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/61320/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":61320,"taskName":"Clean \u0026 Polish Flooring - For Business","taskDescription":"Clean and Polish Vinyl or Wood Flooring - For Business","xmTaskDescriptor":"Floor Cleaners For Your Business","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Clean, polish, vinyl floors, wood floors, business, commercial, strip, wax, buff, for businesses","textMessagingName":"Clean Polish Floor-Biz","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes cleaning, stripping, waxing, buffing, polishing, etc.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes cleaning, stripping, waxing, buffing, polishing, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local commercial contractors to Clean and Polish Vinyl Flooring. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated commercial vinyl floor cleaners in your area.","htmlTitle":"Commercial Floor Cleaning \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e  | \u003ccity\u003e Clean and Polish Floors","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":50,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean and Polish Flooring - For Business","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Clean / Polish Vinyl or Wood Flooring - For Business","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Commercial Cleaning and Polishing Flooring Project","urlName":"Clean-Polish-Vinyl-Flooring-Commercial","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"Commercial Vinyl Floor Cleaning \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e  | \u003ccity\u003e Clean and Polish Vinyl Floors","searchKeywords":"Clean, polish, wood floors, vinyl floors, business, commercial, strip, wax, buff, hardwood","emcCategoryOid":-12014,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":7243,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}